I’m Navi!
Matière of Miare City’s
star detective assistant!
I met Liko and Roy and everyone,
made friends with Metamon,
and my dream of
catching a Pokémon came true!
Riding on the Brave Asagi,
Navi’s adventure now gets going, going!
All right. Fully installed.
You can use that app to quickly contact
any of us, your crewmates!
Yeah! The app’s proof you’re one of us!
Now Navi’s part of the Rising Voltteccers!
Hooray!
Hmph!
I still ain’t accepted you, y’know.
Ult...
I don’t need Ult to accept me!
Navi has Cap’s seal of approval!
Navi! C’mon over, everything’s ready.
Whoa...!
This’ll be your room starting today.
It’s yours to use as you see fit.
Thanks, Orio!
Wait, wasn’t this room...?
Friede’s, yes. He hasn’t been back
to use it even once, so I cleaned it out!
Navi’s room! Navi’s room!
It’s nothin’.
Let’s go, Yamirami!
Ready, set, and... GO! READY! GO!
We’re in top-notch mode
You’re not alone, you know?
Put our palms together, raise them high, and let our lights unite
pOCket Monsters
Wonder Voyage
In rain, gales, or even blizzards
We can laugh together as friends
All of the gaps in the Index
let’s fill them in bit by bit
If you’re trying to be someone else
Don’t think like that
You’re fine just as you are
Don’t lose yourself
Recollect on what’s in your pocket
This is what makes us strong
A heartfelt bond that will never fade
Ready, set, and...
GO! READY! GO!
We’re in top-notch mode
You’re not alone, you know?
Let’s fly, higher and higher!
It’s fine to make mistakes
just rest your wings
When you’ve caught your breath
you can fly off once more!
Come along with us, oh-oh
Voltteccers
Pass the endlessly turning seasons,
and venture into brand-new skies
Navi's Little Big Adventure!
I’m Navi. Nice to meet you!
Let’s be good friends, ‘kay?
There’s still so many faces
left for me to greet!
This is the kitchen.
I prepare everyone’s meals.
Whoa!
And here’s the sweets.
If you have any requests
to add to the menu, let me know.
I can make anything you want.
Navi loves omurice!
Gotcha!
Dinner’s decided, then!
Yay!
Yep. You’re totally healthy.
That’s good to hear.
Molly, thank you!
There’s even a doctor aboard,
that’s amazing!
If you ever feel bad, drop right by.
Keep an eye on Metamon, too.
Keeping your partner in good health
is one of a trainer’s duties, after all.
Partner...
Right!
This is the engine room.
We take coal, and burn it like this...
...and the energy it produces allows
the Brave Asagi to fly through the sky!
Awesome!
But it’s so hot.
Doesn’t look like
it bothers you, does it, Orio?
I’m used to it.
Plus, you could say this room
is the heart of the ship.
It’s an important job, so I enjoy it.
An important job...
Okay, Metamon! We need one, too!
A job?
It’s just so nice how
everyone on the ship is hard at work!
Navi wants to help out
with something, too!
What would you like to try, Navi?
No idea! Anything!
A-Anything, huh...?
Then give everything a try!
First, you can clean the ship with us!
Okay!
That way!
Right.
Miniguru! Miniguru!
Mini Gurumin!
Here!
Thanks.
Yay! This is fun!
Isn’t it so wonderful when everybody
does their part, Metamon?
Huh? Metamon?
Huh?
He’s not doing any job.
Wait, Metamon,
when did you get there?!
Give Navi back her Metamon!
Wh-Wh-What’s going on?!
Nyah-nyah!
The heck’s her problem?!
That cake tasted so good!
Murdock makes the best sweets
in the world!
Yeah! I love ‘em!
Sorry, but can someone go into town
and buy some ingredients for me?
I need something, too.
We’re running low on Potions,
so could you grab some of those, as well?
Errands?! Me! Navi’ll do it!
Thanks.
But I couldn’t let you go alone...
Right.
If someone could go with her...
Blah! I can go by myself!
Ult. You go along with her.
Huh?! Why do I gotta do it?!
You’re not doing anything,
so at least try to be helpful.
What wuzzat?!
You leave me no choice.
Navi’ll let you accompany her on her errand!
You’ve got it backwards!
Dumb little kid!
So says the little kid!
Huh?!
Okay then, we’ll leave it to you two.
Sure!
Geez...
Take care!
We’ll be off!
You think those two’ll be
okay together, though?
Good question.
Hopefully they won’t
end up bickering...
Yeah. That’s why I asked him to go.
Huh?
I bet they just don’t know
each other well enough yet.
Plus, Yamirami and Metamon
get along really well.
With Pokémon by their sides,
they’ll be just fine!
Yeah.
I can see the town!
Amazing!
So many berries!
I told ya not to act hyper!
I’ve never seen these ones before!
I wonder what they taste like.
Want to try one?
Is that okay? Thank you!
Mm! Really juicy!
Out running errands?
Yeah! Navi has a job!
Ooh, good for you!
What are you after?
This was tasty, so I’ll take these!
Hold it! That’s not
what they asked us to get.
Lessee... These, and these...
Aw man, how many did we need...?
Argh! Gimme fifty each!
Oh my! That many?
Three of these, and five of these.
Please and thank you!
Coming right up!
You’re so careless!
Were you even listening to what Murdock said?
Quiet!
What do you mean, “Quiet”?!
You’re bein’ annoying,
so I’m sayin’ be quiet!
You’re the one
who needs to quiet down, Ult!
What wuzzat?!
Metamon.
You’re going to the pharmacy with Navi.
Hey, Navi!
You don’t know what to buy—!
Molly told me, and I remembered!
Geez...
Umm... Was it this way?
The sign said it wasn’t far...
Just... a little bit further...
Where... am I?
pOCket Monsters
Wonder Voyage
I-I’m fine! I’m not lost!
Yeah! The pharmacy’s
right around this corner!
Oh, right!
The Rising Voltteccers app!
They said it could
contact them anytime...
Huh? Huh, huh?
I left it back in my room!
What do I do...?
Huh? She hasn’t been here?
I haven’t seen
a little girl with a Metamon, no.
Well then, for now,
can I get some Potions...
...and the stuff on this note?
Sure. That’ll just be a moment.
Geez...
Where’d that Navi
go wanderin’ off to...?
Huh? “Look for her”?
Count me out.
She’s the one who wandered off on her own.
I got it already!
Well, I am her senior, after all...
When I find her,
I’m givin’ her a piece of my mind.
This is bad!
I can’t find her nowhere!
I should’ve kept a closer eye on her.
If something happens to her...
I’m sorry Metamon
touched your whiskers!
It was probably just
curious about you—
No good! It’s not listening at all!
Metamon, run for it!
Help...
Finally found ya!
Lost little kid!
I never asked you to
come and save me, you know...
Hmph. I ain’t even gonna
lift a finger for ya.
Huh?
Just look.
Metamon... You’re...
It’s rarin’ to fight to protect you.
But Navi’s never done
any kind of battle before...
Navi!
You’re a Pokémon Trainer
who caught a Pokémon, right?
What good’s a trainer
who can’t meet their partner’s feelings?
A Pokémon Trainer...
Don’t worry!
You’ll have my advice!
Go be with Metamon!
Let’s go, Metamon!
Order Metamon to do a move!
Metamon! Transform!
All right! Now you...
You’re tiny!
You’re basically a Koratta!
Don’t sweat it!
It should be able to use Ratta’s moves!
Uhh, what did it do before...?
Bite!
One more time! Bite, Metamon!
Metamon!
This isn’t working...
Don’t stress out!
Keep your eye on your foe!
I already was!
You don’t need to tell me!
Metamon, dodge!
You’re open! Metamon! Bite!
All right!
Awright!
What now? It turned back!
Look around!
You gotta use anything you can in a fight!
Anything I can use...
Transform into Kairyu!
Ooh, you picked Kairyu?
Hehe! The tables turn!
Metamon! Twister!
Metamon, put all your might
into a Twister!
No way...
Danger incoming!
Metamon, escape to the sky!
Ahh! It’s turning back again!
I’ve gotta do something!
Navi! Don’t take your gaze off Metamon!
But—!
You always gotta
keep your partner in mind!
The only one
Metamon can rely on is you!
Metamon still hasn’t given up!
And neither has Navi...
That’s it!
Metamon!
Transform into the rock you sleep as!
Whoa, that’s hard!
We did it... Metamon!
That was great!
That was the best!
Huh? Huh, huh?
When I relaxed,
all my strength suddenly just...
Are that little one’s fangs
gonna be okay?
Don’t you worry!
Ratta’s teeth grow back naturally,
even if they break off. I ain’t worried.
Huh... Ult, you know so much!
Course. ‘Cause I’ve been studyin’.
Hey, what did you think of our battle?
Well, pretty good
for a first-timer, I s’pose.
Ult, thank you!
Still nowhere near
being strongest, y’hear?!
Kairyu! Fly faster, like whoosh!
Huh?
Kairyu, you’re amazing!
Oh, they’re back!
Welcome back!
We’re back...
Good work, you two.
Yeah!
Listen, listen!
I battled a wild Pokémon!
Metamon won against a Ratta!
That’s amazing!
Hehe! Navi is Metamon’s trainer,
after all!
Sounds like you had a fun adventure.
Ult, thank you.
Well, I am her senior, after all!
‘Course I’d support the newbie.
By the way, you two...
Where’s the stuff you went out for?
Oh...
Aw, geez!
I left it back in town!
What’s with you?!
You’re such a dope!
I had to go looking for you—!
Enough! Just go get it already!
No little kid’s orderin’ me around!
You’re the little kid here, Ult!
You always get mad so fast!
What? I ain’t mad, got me?!
Yes you are!
Am not!
Huh?
Time for breakfast!
Make sure you eat up good.
I see. So he does have a job.
Huh? Oh, Metamon!
You hungry too?
Here.
They get along well.
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Friede here!
It’s time to Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie!
Today’s topic is Ratta!
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Ratta
Classification
Type
Height
Weight
Abilities
Mouse Pokémon
Normal
Fleet-Footed
Guts
This Pokémon is
more violent than it looks.
It has a chubby body,
but do you know what part of it helps it keep balance?
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
See the answer after the commercials!
Oh! One toss makes a red-white-spinny-shaky
Cutesy Capsule
One click makes a rolly-wobbly-all-aflutter
onlooking Street
One toss makes a red-white-spinny-shaky
Cutesy Capsule
One click makes a rolly-wobbly-all-aflutter
onlooking Street
Gonna give my motivation button a little tap!
The power of hard work is amazing!
(Ahem!)
But if I slack off I might end up devolving...
Well, that’s no good!
But now you mention it...
I know button mashing won’t help at all
So stop shaking this maiden’s heart already
(Stop it!)
Getting attached, but then they turn away
When things just don’t go the way that you want...
Isn’t it so fun? Doesn’t it make your heart race?
Doesn’t it make you all excited?
When I feel a spark...
I’ll catch it in a Cutesy Capsule
Face to face with the dream I’ve always imagined...
I’ve got electric jolts running through me!
I’m so lovey-dovey I can’t even move!
When I know change is still inside of me...
I’ll catch it in a Cutesy Capsule
then we can be together forever
We’ll conquer any obstacle!
I know our future will shine!
So let’s be friends!
Pick up you! I want you! Hit chu straight in the heart!
Pick up you! I want you! We’re right at the peak of our adven-chu!!
Oh! One toss makes a red-white-spinny-shaky
Cutesy Capsule
One click makes a rolly-wobbly-all-aflutter
onlooking Street
One toss makes a red-white-spinny-shaky
Cutesy Capsule
One click makes a rolly-wobbly-all-aflutter
onlooking Street
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Time to announce
the correct answer!
The answer is...
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
Its fangs
Its whiskers
Its tail
B: Its whiskers!
Its whiskers
Ratta treasure their whiskers.
Touch them, and they’ll get mad and Bite back!
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Sorry about earlier.
Take this.
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Watch out...!
Amazing!
Next episode
Hey, hey, hey!
Whoa! What’s going on?!
Bringing you the choicest of scoops
that’ll blow you away!
This time, we delve into the riddles of
the Pokémon lurking in the Land of Mystery!
Next episode
Sohnano!
That’s right!
Who’s this guy?
A new member
of the Rising Voltteccers, I take it?
I’m Sohtim da Yotim, a.k.a. Sohdayo!
Next episode
Ever pursuing the Unfabricated Truth—
A-And so! To be continued
next time on Pocket Monsters!
Astonishing! Mega Rekkuuza and the Land of Mystery?!
Huh.
Mega Rekkuuza?!